# **Tunere Ereibor**

A skilled full-stack Node.js developer with expertise in Agile methodology and a passion for delivering quality code. Possessing experience in developing applications with a focus on scalability and performance. A dedicated team player committed to achieving project goals and delivering results.

6 Hudu Dan Mallam, Dei dei, Dakwa, Abuja, Nigeria. +2347033940439

E Mail: <u>Tunere Ereibor</u> LinkedIn: <u>Tunere Ereibor</u> Github: <u>Tunere Ereibor</u>

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Decagon, Lagos** — *Software Engineer*

JANUARY 2023 - PRESENT

- Developed RESTful and GraphQL APIs using Node.js with proficiency in MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL and SQLite databases.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to ensure successful delivery of projects using Agile methodology and Scrum framework.
- Utilized React and EJS for dynamic front-end development to enhance user experience.
- Implemented Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment (CI/CD) processes to automate the software development lifecycle, improving the efficiency and quality of software releases.

# Nigeria Police Force, Abuja — Network Admin

MARCH 2021 - MARCH 2022

- Collaborated with other IT professionals to troubleshoot and resolve network issues, including connectivity problems and software malfunctions.
- Configured and managed network equipment, including routers and switches.

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- React Hooks
- Next.js
- Tailwind CSS
- Express.js
- REST API
- GraphQL
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL
- SQLite
- Heroku
- Digital Ocean
- Firebase
- lira
- •Test-Driven Development
- Docker
- CI/CD
- Git and GitHub

## **PROJECTS**

# **E-Aid Application:**

E-Aid application is a health-tech product that allows users to have access to verified medical experts through the app. It will allow the users to see hospitals closest to them and help them to get expert advice in the case of an emergency.

Technologies Used: Node.js, TypeScript, MySQL, Express.js

**Link**: E-Aid Application

## **QuickGrade Application:**

QuickGrade application is an examination management system designed to simplify the exam-taking and administration process for students and lecturers, as well as provide them with a clear quick understanding of their exam results.

Technologies Used: Node.js, React, TypeScript, SQlite, Express.js

**Link**: QuickGrade Application

### **EDUCATION**

**Igbinedion University Okada, Edo State** — BSc Second Class Lower - Computer Science and Information Technology

SEPTEMBER 2016 - OCTOBER 2020